minato-jf.jp 2019-04-05

# JF Japanese e-Learning Minato - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### For users within the EEA (European Economic Area), please be sure to thoroughly read and understand the Special notes before use.

#### (General Provision)

  1. “The Japan Foundation Japanese-Language Institute, Kansai” (hereinafter referred to as “the Institute”) operating the website of “JF Japanese e-Learning _Minato_ ” (hereinafter referred to as “This Site”), respects the privacy of users of all contents and services in This Site (hereinafter referred to as “Users”) and exerts extreme caution in the managing of Users’ personal information.  
In addition, hereinafter this “JF Japanese e-Learning _Minato_ Privacy Policy” is referred to as “This Policy”. 
  2. The Institute handles personal information obtained from Users through the operation of This Site according to “The Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information by Independent Administrative Institutions” of Japan, “[PRIVACY POLICY](http://www.jpf.go.jp/e/privacy/index.html)” of The Japan Foundation, and “Privacy Protection Regulations of the Japan Foundation”.

#### (Personal Information)

  3. All words and terms used in This Policy shall be interpreted in accordance with “Privacy Policy” of the Japan Foundation. Therefore, any provisions which are not stated in This Policy shall be interpreted and operated according to “[PRIVACY POLICY](http://www.jpf.go.jp/e/privacy/index.html)” of The Japan Foundation.

#### (Collecting of Personal Information)

  4. The Institute collects Users’ Personal Information by just and legitimate methods, and not by illegal methods that are contrary to Users’ will.
  5. The Institute notifies Users of, or publishes the purpose of, the use of Personal Information preliminarily.

#### (The purpose of Use of Personal Information)

  6. The Institute uses Personal Information collected from Users for the purpose of operation of This Site and other sites that the Institute operates. The main purposes of use are as follows. 
    1. (1) To provide Japanese online courses and other services that the Institute provides (hereinafter referred to as “the Service”) to Users and to give Users notice(s) relating to the Service;
    2. (2) To give Users notice about the pass/fail status of Japanese online Course, etc.;
    3. (3) To respond to an inquiry from Users;
    4. (4) To caution or warn against Users who violate any of the terms and conditions of the Service;
    5. (5) To make or to analyze statistical data, and to make or to carry out a questionnaire related to This Site and the Service;
    6. (6) To Confirm the identity of Users when the Institute receives requests for disclosure, alternation, addition, or deletion registration information;

#### (Provision of Personal Information to Third Party)

  7. The Institute does not provide or disclose Personal Information to any third party without the Users’ approval or permission; however, this shall not apply to the following cases: 
    1. (1) When the Users have agreed to disclosure;
    2. (2) When the information is disclosed or offered as masked data;
    3. (3) When the disclosing or offering is permitted by the laws and/or regulations of Japan;
    4. (4) When the disclosing or offering is required by a public agency based upon the laws and/or regulations of Japan;
    5. (5) When the Institute delegates some or all of the Service to any third party for the purpose of providing the Service;
    6. (6) When the Institute relegates some or all of the Service to any third party;

#### (Usage of Access Log and IP Address by the Institute)

  8. The Institute is able to collect information related to Users’ privacy by using access log, IP address, etc. Information about likes or interests, browsing history, etc. is collected by using the access log, IP address, etc.  
In addition, the Institute is able to use such information without any limitation as long as the Institute uses the information in a format that makes it impossible to identify the individual and that makes it impossible to check against or to inquire for Personal Information. 

#### (Modification of Purpose of Use, etc.)

  9. Modification of This Policy by the Institute: such as a change of purpose of use, change of method of management, etc. should become effective immediately when the Institute uploads the updated This Policy on This Site.

#### (Exclusion of Liability)

  10. The Institute does not accept any liability for the protection of privacy from website linked to This Site. Users shall access or visit external linked website at their own risk.
  11. The Institute exercises reasonable efforts to prevent all collected information from being disclosed to any third party accidentally; however, despite the security system of The Japan Foundation, should any information be accidentally leaked, the Institute assumes no liability and responsibility for any divulging of personally identifiable information.

#### (Chief Administrator)

  12. The Institute appoints the following desk to be Chief Administrator of Personal Information, and tries to manage Personal Information appropriately and to improve the enforcement of policies related to the protection of Personal Information continuously. In addition, the following desk should be the contact for inquiries about Personal Information at the Institute.

Privacy Protection Desk, Educational Training Section,  
Japan Foundation Japanese-Language Institute, Kansai  
3-14 Rinku Port Kita, Tajiri-cho, Sennan-gun, Osaka 598-0093, Japan  
Tel: 0724-90-2601, Fax: 0724-90-2801 

#### 

The Japan Foundation (the “ **JF** ”) shall comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “ **GDPR** ”) and other applicable national laws (“ **applicable laws** ”) in connection with the provision of any of the services that the JF provides (the “ **Services** ”) to users (the “ **Users** ”) in the European Economic Area (the “ **EEA** ”, and the countries that are members of the EEA are individually or collectively referred to as “ **EEA member countries** ”), and therefore hereby establishes this Privacy Policy (this “ **Privacy Policy** ”) in order to appropriately process the personal data and other data of Users in the EEA.

  1. Processing Personal data, etc. 
    1. (1) Definitions  
“ **Personal data** ” means any data relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, including, without limitation, names, addresses, dates of birth, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and any other information collected in connection with providing the Services.  
“ **Processing** ” means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data, etc. or on sets of personal data, etc., whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction. 

    2. (2) Purpose of use of personal data, etc.   
The JF will process the Users’ personal data to provide, improve and develop the Services.   
In the case of processing the Users’ personal data for purposes other than the above, the JF will notify Users in advance of such new purposes of use and other matters as required by applicable laws.   
By manifesting their intention to consent to this Privacy Policy, Users will be deemed to have consented to the processing of their personal data by the JF within the scope of the above purpose of use, and The JF will process the Users’ personal data based on such Users’ consent; provided, however, that Users may withdraw such consent at any time. Even in that case, this will not affect the lawfulness of processing performed pursuant to consent before the Users’ withdrawal thereof.   
The personal data that Users are to provide is necessary in order for the JF to provide the Service to the Users, and there may be cases in which Users who have not provided such data will be unable to use the Service. 

    3. (3) Retention Period   
The JF will retain the Users’ personal data as long as the JF requires such data for achieving the purpose of use specified above. 

    4. (4) Transfer   
The JF may share the Users’ personal data obtained by its overseas offices including those in London, Paris, Madrid, Rome, Cologne and Budapest with other offices including the headquarter in Japan, and may provide such data to third parties such as cloud vendors and outside contractors of the JF, etc., to implement the purpose of use specified above. Countries located outside the EEA (including, without limitation, Japan, the same shall apply hereafter) are among the third parties to whom the JF will disclose the Users’ personal data, and the Users shall be deemed to have consented to the following matters by consenting to this Privacy Policy:   

      1. (a) In the case that the country in which the third party is located is outside the EEA, such country does not have the same data protection laws as EEA member countries, i.e., many of the rights provided to data subjects in the EEA may not be given; 
      2. (b) The Users’ personal data will be provided and processed for the purpose specified above; and 
      3. (c) The Users’ personal data will be provided to third parties located outside the EEA. 
  
In addition to the above, in the case that the JF provides the Users’ personal data to a third party located in a country outside the EEA, the JF will ensure that adequate measures such as standard contract clauses based on the GDPR are taken concerning the protection of the Users’ personal data. 

    5. (5) Rights of Users   
The Users may request from the JF access to, rectification or erasure of, and restriction of processing of their personal data, may object to the processing of the Users’ personal data, and may request data portability. The JF accepts such Users’ requests at the contact point set forth in “3. Contact” below.   
The JF may refuse the Users’ requests if the JF deems that there is no basis for such Users’ requests or if they are deemed excessive.   
The Users may raise objections with the data protection authorities having jurisdiction over the location of the Users’ domicile with regard to the processing of their personal data. 

  2. Safety Management Measures
In order to protect from unauthorized access to personal data, loss, etc. of personal data, taking into account the type of personal data, the degree of sensitivity and the degree of economic influence and mental harm caused to Users in the case of a personal data breach, the JF comprehensively evaluates and judges the risks of personal data breaches, implements appropriate personal, organizational and technical safety management measures based on the risk of a personal data breach, if necessary, checks such safety management measures, sets up a process for correction, and constantly strives to improve security.  
The JF shall strive to appropriately manage personal data by restricting the entry of outsiders into the offices which are processing personal data, conducting educational awareness activities for all officers and employees involved in the protection of personal data, and placing a manager in charge for each division processing personal data. 
  3. Contact
In the event of Users having any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or the processing of personal data by The JF or having any requests concerning the access to, rectification of, erasure of, or restriction of processing of personal data, or regarding data portability, please contact the JF.  
The contact information for The JF is as follows: 

Privacy Protection Desk, Educational Training Section,  
Japan Foundation Japanese-Language Institute, Kansai  
3-14 Rinku Port Kita, Tajiri-cho, Sennan-gun, Osaka 598-0093, Japan  
Tel: 0724-90-2601, Fax: 0724-90-2801 

Effective as of July 27, 2016  
Amended as of May 24, 2018
